Finding Aid for Frank D. Stella papers, ca. 1940-2010.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Various community, fraternal, and charitable activities
  - WTVS, Detroit Public Television, Channel 56 circa 1990-1994 (Box 44)
    (Stella was elected chairman of the board of the Detroit Educational Television Foundation in 1990)
  - Ste. Anne de Detroit (Tricentennial Jubilee 1701-2001) circa 2001 (Box 45)
    (FS was co-chairman of the celebration)
  - Solanus Casey capital campaign files 1999-2002 (Box 46)
    (a Capuchin Franciscan ministry in Detroit)
  - St. Vincent de Paul development campaign files 1999-2002 (Box 46)
  - Detroit Casino Gaming Study Commission 1988 (Box 47)
    (FS was a member of the Commission Executive Committee)
- Photographs
  The Photographs series contains autographed photos collected by Stella and photographs of Stella at various events. The Autographed Photos subseries contains autographed photos of politicians, prominent Italian dignitaries, and celebrities. It includes both autographed headshots and autographed photos of Stella with various figures. Prominent autographs include those of Presidents Gerald Ford, Ronald Reagan, George Bush, Bill Clinton, and George W. Bush; Michigan Governors Romney, Milliken, and Engler; and celebrities Perry Como, Sophia Loren, and Luciano Pavarotti. The Selections from Albums subseries contains photographs removed from albums Stella maintained in addition to seven complete albums. The photographs are arranged in rough chronological order, based on the dates of the photos contained in the original albums. These photographs are mainly of Stella at a variety of events, including ceremonies honoring him and NIAF Gala dinners. These photographs also feature Stella posing with a variety of celebrities and prominent politicians.
  - With wife and family members (Box 48)
    include Stella in clown outfit and onstage with rose in hand
  - Early photos relating to business and facilities 1940s, 1950s (Box 48)
    (many of the photos have been partially burned)
  - Politicians
    (include many autographed photos)
    - Bush, George (includes Barbara Bush) (Box 48)
    - Bush, George W. (Box 48)
    - Clinton, Bill (Box 48)
      also see oversized Box 49
    - Dole, Robert (includes Pat Leahy) (Box 48)
    - Domenici, Pete (Box 48)
    - Engler, John (Box 48)
    - Ford, Gerald (Box 48)
    - Giuliani, Rudy (Box 48)
    - Griffin, Bob (Box 48)
    - McCain, John (Box 48)
    - Milliken, William (Bill) (Box 48)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Mondale, Walter (Box 48)
    - Nixon, Richard and family members (Box 48)
    - Quayle, Dan (includes Marilyn Quayle) (Box 48)
    - Reagan, Ronald (includes Nancy Reagan) (Box 48)
    - Romney, George (Box 48)
    - Schultz, George (Box 48)
  - Other public figures
    - Como, Perry (Box 48)
    - Fisher, Max (Box 48)
    - Gaddafi, Muammar (Box 48)
    - Italian Figures (Box 48)
    - Loren, Sophia (Box 48)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Pavarotti, Luciano (Box 48)
    - Pope John Paul II (Box 48)
    - Sports Figures (Box 48)
    - Teresa, Mother (Box 48)
  - Oversized photographs
    - Autographed photos, 9 photographs (Box 49)
    - Distinguished Clown Corps, 4 photographs (Box 49)
    - Reagan, Ronald, 2 photographs (Box 49)
    - Stella, Frank, 2 photographs (Box 49)
    - White House, 1 photograph (Box 49)
  - Albums and Selections from Albums
    - Selections
      - Album 1 circa 1940-1955 (Box 48)
      - Album 2 1942-1946 (Box 48)
      - Album 3 1970-1971 (Box 48)
      - Album 4 circa 1973-1980 (Box 48)
      - Album 5 1977-1981 (Box 48)
      - Album 6 1978-1989 (Box 48)
      - Album 7 1979-1984 (Box 48)
      - Album 8 circa 1980-1983 (Box 48)
      - Album 9 1981-1983 (Box 48)
      - Album 10 circa 1982-1990 (Box 48)
      - Album 11 1982-1995 (Box 48)
      - Album 12 1984 (Box 48)
      - Album 13 1984-1985 (Box 48)
      - Album 14 1984-1987 (Box 48)
      - Album 15 1984-1987 (Box 48)
      - Album 16 1984-1989 (Box 48)
      - Album 17 1984-1991 (Box 48)
      - Album 18 1984-1991 (Box 48)
      - Album 19 1984-1995 (Box 48)
      - Album 20 1984-1998 (Box 48)
      - Album 21 (Paris) 1985 (Box 48)
      - Album 22 1985-1994 (Box 48)
      - Album 23 circa 1985-2001 (Box 48)
      - Album24 1991-1992 (Box 48)
      - Album 25 1991-1996 (Box 48)
      - Album 26 1992-1996 (Box 48)
      - Album 27 circa 1993 (Box 48)
      - Album 28 1994-2002 (Box 48)
      - Album 29 1995-1997 (Box 48)
      - Album 30 1996 (Box 48)
      - Album 31 1997 (Box 48)
      - Album 32 1997-1999 (Box 48)
      - Album 33 circa 2000 (Box 48)
      - F. D. Stella Products Company, loose photographs from album (Box 48)
      - Italy circa 1985 (Box 48)
      - Loose photos (Box 48)
      - NIAF Dinner circa 1995 (Box 48)
      - Portraits, also see oversized Box 2 (Box 48)
    - Photograph albums
      - Rome 1986 (Volume 1)
      - Circolo di Roma undated (Volume 2)
      - F. D. Stella Products Company circa 1965 (Volume 3)
      - Port of Games Guest of Honor 1985 (Volume 4)
      - Greater Detroit Chamber of Commerce 1983-1984 (Volume 5)
      - Miscellaneous events circa 1984 (Volume 6)
      - Miscellaneous events 1992-1994 (Volume 7)
      - Republican Party events and politicians 1992-1994: (Volume 11)
        include Gerald Ford, John Connally, William Milliken, Henry Kissinger, Ronald Reagan, and other Michigan and national politicians
      - Miscellaneous personal and public events 1980s: (Volume 12)
        include Ronald Reagan, George Bush, Frank Sinatra, Max Fisher, Sophia Loren, Bob Dole, and Charlton Heston